worldwidemusicexpo.com 2013-07-31

# Privacy Policy- Celebrity How Tos And Entertainment

PRIVACY POLICY

At WorldWideMusicExpo.com, we are committed to protecting your privacy. Any information we collect, such as email addresses, is submitted at the visitor’s will. We do not and will not share any personal information with any third parties unless by governmental order..

 **Cookies**

All browsers offer “cookies” and if you permit their use, they will store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to the site that placed the cookie. A cookie is a small text file. It is not a program, or a plug-in. It could not be used as a virus, and it cannot access your hard drive. Cookies simply assist in  
tracking which features you like the most and allow content to be customized upon your return, according to prior preferences at that site. They would not gather or hold any personal information. At WorldWideMusicExpo.com, WWME , We may use cookies to:

You also have flexible choices in respect to cookies. By simply modifying your browser preferences, you have the right to choose whether:

However, please note that if you reject some or all cookies, your experience at our sites and on other sites throughout the web may not be completed. Some sites require cookies to function, such as those with e-commerce features. In addition, if you disable cookies, you will not be eligible to take advantage of personalized content delivery offered by us or other Internet sites.

Consumers have the unrestricted ability to opt out of all WWME support forms at any time by simply emailing admin.

The unique user identification number, associated with when and how many times an individual has seen an advertisement, is deleted after 90 days of user inactivity. These unique IDs are not tied to any personally identifiable information. Aggregated statistical information, such as the popularity of an advertiser campaign, will be retained as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

Log files are created to analyze trends, keep track of user movement in the aggregate and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. Log file data may be retained for up to a maximum period of fifteen months.

Registering to become a member of the WWME online advertising network, either as an advertiser or a publisher, requires the submission of Personally Identifiable information to our company. This can include your full name, mailing and/or billing address, email address, company name, and website URL. We use this information to service your accounts and respond to inquiries. Communications to our business users are related to the Advertising Network. We hold all such information submitted in strict confidence. Under no circumstances will a user's email address, mailing address, phone number, or other Personally Identifiable information be sold to, supplied to, or otherwise made available to any third party. Registered members who wish to update or correct their personal information can contact us through our online form.

At Our Sites While we use cookies in other parts of our website, cookies received with the payment processes are placed by our Payment Services provider. We do not have access to these cookies or any information that they may contain. Please contact the Payment Services provider for more information as noted above.

This site contains links to other sites. WorldWideMusicExpo.com, WWME Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites once you have left our site. We only link to general audience sites but cannot be responsible for any redirection or content changes over which we  
have no control. Please contact us immediately by emailing us if there is a problem with any of our links.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your concern about this website, please contact: webmaster @ worldwidemusicexpo
